config = {"app_name": "Jake's XMAS Quiz",
          "theme": "christmas"}

questions = [{"question": "In which land is it 'Always winter but never Christmas'?",
              "answers": ["Lapland", "Narnia", "North Pole", "Africa"],
              "correct_answer": 1,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "In which month does Christmas fall in Australia?",
              "answers": ["December", "January", "July", "June"],
              "correct_answer": 0,
              "points": 1,
              },
              {"question": "How many children did Bob Cratchit have in 'A Christmas Carol'?",
              "answers": ["One", "Two", "Six", "Eight"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "Which European country was the first to issue a Chistmas stamp?",
              "answers": ["Poland", "Luxembourg", "UK", "Austria"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "The carol 'Silent Night' was written in which country?",
              "answers": ["Poland", "Luxembourg", "UK", "Austria"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "Who sang the opening line of 'Do They Know It's Christmas' for Band Aid II in 1989?",
              "answers": ["Bananarama", "Cliff Richard", "Kylie Minogue", "Cathy Dennis"],
              "correct_answer": 2,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "Where does the Queen normally spend Christmas Day?",
              "answers": ["Buckingham", "Windsor", "Kensington", "Sandringham"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "What colour is Father Christmas' belt?",
              "answers": ["White", "Brown", "Gold", "Black"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "What did 'Frosty the Snowman' have for a nose?",
              "answers": ["A carrot", "Coal", "A stone", "A button"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "On what date did the Twelfth night occur?",
              "answers": ["January 5th", "January 4th", "January 6th", "January 7th"],
              "correct_answer": 0,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "Which US state was the last to declare Christmas a holiday?",
              "answers": ["South Dakota", "Oklahoma", "California", "Hawaii"],
              "correct_answer": 1,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "With which seasonal product did J C Hall make his millions?",
              "answers": ["Christmas Trees", "Christmas Songs", "Wrapping Paper", "Christmas Cards"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "What was sent on the 11th Day of the Twelve days of Christmas?",
              "answers": ["Pipers", "Doves", "Maids", "Drummers"],
              "correct_answer": 0,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "What present did Harry Potter receive from Hagrid in his first Christmas at Hogwarts?",
              "answers": ["An invisibility cloak", "A wooden flute", "An owl", "A wolly hat"],
              "correct_answer": 1,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "Which position did 'Fairy-tale of New York' reach?",
              "answers": ["Number 1", "Number 2", "Number 4", "Number 6"],
              "correct_answer": 1,
              "points": 10,
              },
              {"question": "Who has the most UK Christmas number ones?",
              "answers": ["Muse", "The Beatles", "Oasis", "The Rolling Stones"],
              "correct_answer": 1,
              "points": 5,
              },
              {"question": "Which physicist, responsible for formulating the laws of motion, was born on Christmas Day 1642",
              "answers": ["Albert Einstein", "Galileo Galilei", "Niels Bohr", "Isaac Newton"],
              "correct_answer": 3,
              "points": 10,
              }
]
